

+1 (480) 572-4421



🖄 Chandler AZ



hadas.gadish@gmail.com



in hadas-kamin



Hadasss



PORTFOLIO

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts, Political **Science** / Ben-Gurion University Israel / graduated with honors

Fullstack Web Development / University of Arizona / 99 Average

web development / she codes;

The Complete Javascript Course / Udemy

SKILLS



VOLUNTEER WORK

June 2021-Present

she codes; front-end track coordinator

June 2021-Present

Code for Israel front-end developer

LANGUAGES

English: highly proficient Hebrew: native speaker

HADAS KAMIN

Junior Fullstack Developer

ABOUT ME

Aspiring fullstack developer, self-taught since early 2021, currently a UofA boot camp student, graduating end of May.

On a career change path from being an accomplished marketing specialist with 15 years' experience and enjoying my newfound passion!

I am: target and result oriented; Excellent interpersonal, verbal, and written communication skills; Positive, Can-Do attitude, great collaboration skills within an organization as well as external stakeholders.

KEY STRENGTHS

Autodidact - Self Starter - Adaptable - Strong Logical & Analytical Skills - Project Management - Problem Solving - Detail Oriented - Inter-departmental Collaboration - Team Player!

PROJECTS AND PORTFOLIO

PORTFOLIO

Day Planner | Coding Quiz | Weather API App Marvel API Hero Finder Favorites Dashboard

WORK EXPERIENCE

In my previous roles I did managed many operations that may not be required in a dev position but they attest to my being a hard worker, having an all-in and positive attitude, which I believe are key to succeed in any role. Some of my previous roles:

Brand Manager Neopharm Consumer Products / Israel / 2017 – 2018 Oversaw 360° brand life cycle. Initiated and implemented marketing strategies, accountable for launches and delivery, P&L reports and budget status.

Digital Marketing Communication Manager Israel Credit Cards / Israel / 2015 – 2016 Monitored, analyzed, and executed all advertising activities in the credit (personal loan) field. Close work with R&D on all dev cycle – specification document to deployment, through production and various version releases.

Advertising Manager Mish'an Senior Living / Israel / 2014 – 2015 Managed all marketing, advertising and PR activities for a chain of 13 senior living homes. Developed the digital infrastructure. Tight working relations with sales.

Google AdWords Manager IBP Digital Ad Agency / Israel / 2013 – 2014 Hands on SEM account management.

Account Supervisor Yehoshua\TBWA Ad Agency / Tel Aviv, Israel / 2008 – 2012 In charge of all clients' advertising activities while representing both client and agency interests. Managed six account managers. Strategic planning and production.